

johnnyramsay81@gmail.com |+0044 07737731448 | Leighton Buzzard | github | Linkedin

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a passionate developer with a love for creating robust and beautiful web applications. During 3 years of study I have honed my skills in front-end technologies like Angular, React and also Django, as well as back-end technologies like Node.js, MySQL and PostgreSQL. I consider myself to be a good team-player with strong communication skills. I am very keen to gain entry into the tech industry and become part of an exciting development team where I can learn and contribute!

TECHNICAL SKILLSET

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, Python,

Databases: MySQL, Postgres

Frameworks: Django, jQuery, Bootstrap, Angular, React

· Version Control: Git, GitHub

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

- Spotify Angular App Angular App connected to the Spotify API to view the latest tracks and playlists found on the platform of my favorite Djs. Technologies Used - HTML5, SCSS with Bootstrap, JavaScript, Angular. GitHub - Spotify Api
- Planet Fact Site S simple website showing facts about our planets. Technologies Used HTML5,
 CSS, bootstrap. GitHub Planets
- My Sustainable Life.com E-commerce site for ethical and sustainable goods. Technologies Used
 HTML5, CSS with Bootstrap, JavaScript, Python, Django framework, Postgres DB, Heroku,
 Stripe API for payments and AWS for hosting media. GitHub My Sustainable Life
- Counselling Booking system A site for booking appointments with a counsellor. Technologies
 Used HTML5, CSS with Bootstrap, JavaScript, Python, Django framework, Postgres DB,
 Cloudinary GitHub Counselling Booking System

CERTIFICATES

- Web Dev Simplified JavaScript simplified course.
- Udemy Complete Angular 14

EDUCATION

May 2021-May 2022 Diploma in Full Stack Software Development

Code Institute - Dublin, Ireland - (Credit Rated by University of West of Scotland)

September 2004–June 2007 NVQ3 in Domestic Plumbing and Gas Studies

College of North West London, UK

September 1996–June 2000 Bachelor of Arts, Sport, Health and leisure with Media Studies
Leeds University, UK

EXPERIENCE

December 2021–Present

Gas Service Engineer - TSG Ltd

- Servicing Boilers and heating systems in domestic properties
- Entering technical data from appointment into PDA to generate certificates

January 2021 – December 2021

Gas Service Engineer - APS Ltd

- Servicing Boilers and heating systems in domestic properties
- Entering technical data from appointment into PDA to generate certificates

September 2014 – December 2021

Gas and Plumbing Engineer - Even Flow Building Ltd

- Responsible for Installing and maintaining gas and plumbing systems in properties.
- Ensuring that all works are carried out under the legal obligations set out in the relevant health and safety regulations.
- Ordering new parts and keeping clients updated with relevant work.

April 2011 - August 2014

Assistant Language Teacher in Japan

Working at Elementary, Junior High school and Kindergartens all over Japan.

INTERESTS AND ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Currently learning Angular Tutorials.EU
- I'm currently building a Counsellor Website for a friend using Angular.
- Languages Fluent English, Advanced beginner Japanese, Beginner Spanish, currently learning Tagalog.